Hi, and this is awesome. I will show you quickly how you can use the Cursor.
I will do really quick overview of what you can use from an interface, how you can use some
main features. It will be really short lesson and in details, I will go for every feature in the
next lesson. So this lesson is just needed that you have idea how it works in general and what you
can do. I will create a new project which I will call Winsoft. I will open it from my folder.
I need to create a new folder. Winsoft and I open it. Okay, now we will create a new file. We will
be implementing the utility for check password strings. And this utility will check if the
password you provided to this utility is a weak or strong or very strong. Yeah. And the first
thing I want to show you is how the Cursor understands the context of what we're doing.
When you will create a file, I will provide a name, the player name, what the utility is.
And Cursor will take this file name and you understand the context of what we're creating.
And based on this name, he can do some suggestions. So let's create a password
string check. Checker.js. Oh, we have a name. And when I will start type in class, we implement it.
Winsoft already suggests the name for us. And you see if a press stop, I can implement the next
part. He suggests, okay. So what else? Okay, now he suggests us to create the class instance
and just log the result. Okay, that's great. Now I want to show you how to work with the chat.
So we have the mods right in chat. I will switch to chat mode because I gonna ask some questions.
And I don't ask because I see the check method is not implemented here. So I want to
implement it. But I first, I will ask how as a Winsoft sees implementation of this method.
I'll do use C and implementation of the check password strands method.
Okay, he can understand we have a class. He's analyzing the file. He's proposing some edit.
Okay, we see it did some suggestions. So the method, you know, a lot of logic. And he's
providing some summary. So, okay, there is a method check and he implemented some scoring system.
So he'll check for the lens of the passwords for the character types. One point for each
lower case, upper case and numbers. There are some special characters, which will get two points
for symbols and there is some pattern detection. It's minus two points for some common patterns
like one, two, three, four, five, six, a password to something else. And there are some
categories of how our password is strong or weak. Yeah. And he will provide it with output.
Okay, nice. So let's do the implementation. We can scroll and click just apply.
And we will see all the code right here.
We see if there is no password, the password is required. Then there are some checks
and the method to do the checks. Okay, nice. I'm not going to analyze the implementation. Of
course, it can be better always, but we just apply it and he will click a sub changes right here.
So let's check how it works. I will run the terminal, just run my script,
not any. I'm lazy. I will just click rename to copy the file name.
Okay, we see the score of our password is one. The maximum score is 10. It's really weak
because there is a feedback. We need to include upper case letters, numbers,
special characters and avoid common patterns and repeated characters. Okay, let's make it
something like, okay, he already suggested to do it. Okay, it's a six.
What do we missed? And now common patterns, it would come on patterns and repeated
characters. Okay, if we, I don't know. Let's create something like this.
Okay, it's 80%. It's eight. The password is excellent. We did all the checks, but of course,
there are any improvements. So I think we cannot have a 10 or we cannot have 10. Okay, but that's
area for improvements always. Let me show you some other features like line shots. So you can
select any area and just ask a question about this part of code or ask to implement
something or fix it. For example, I want to add more common patterns. I can just click on edit
or common eye if you're on mark or control eye if you're on window and just extend it with more
variants. Okay, he added more variants. Okay, I just click a step. So you see there is also a line
shot. For example, as another one, what you can do, for example, if you break something, I don't know,
check prints. So and we can collect it and click fix method name, fix wrong method name.
You see, he did a fix. Oh, this is it. All I did it quick already or so. You can use the other
complete. You know, you can use a chat for asking the questions. You can also use a line chat. You
can also select some area of code and ask the fix or improve it. And in much more details,
you will go through all this feature in the next lesson. So, see you.